Changes between Print Schema Documentation v0.95 and Print Schema Documentation v1.0 include:

•	Changed instances of the psf:PageImagableSize Property & child properties to use the Print Schema Keywords namespace.
•	Edited 2.1.3.1.2 to clarify interpretation of vendor-defined values in the UnitType Property.
•	Edited Example 9-12 changing datatypes from xs:string to xs:Qname.
•	Added detailed descriptions of collation settings interactions to 9.3.1. 
•	Edited Table 9-28 for clarity.
•	Edited Table 9-29 for clarity. 
•	Changed references in Example 10–1 from “PageImageableSize" to "PageOutputQuality".
•	Edited 16.4: Added Windows note.

Changes between Print Schema Documentation v1.0 and Print Schema Documentation v1.0a (revision A) include:

•	Changed license from Technical Documentation Agreement to Print Schema License Agreement.
•	Corrected known typographical errors.
•	Updated document version, date, copyright link.
•	Updated Table of Contents, examples and figures with correct page numbers.


Changes between Print Schema Documentation v1.0a and Print Schema Documentation v1.1 include:
•	Added chapter 17, 18 
•	Added a new parameter type for numeric strings 
•	Changed JobComment MaxLength property description to indicate it may be greater or equal in value to the MinLength property.  
•	Changed PageWatermarkTextColor description to indicate MaxLength MUST be 9. 
•	Resolved a number of inconsistencies in the specification around data types and conformance requirements for various keywords 
•	Resolved issues with  Parameter definition rules and the associated examples  
•	Updated document version, date. 
•	Updated Table of Contents, examples, and figures with correct page numbers.
